Guide to the Franz R. and Kathryn M. Stenzel Research Files on Western American Art
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1941-1986; Series VII; 5.67; (14 boxes)
  - Kennedy, Michael
    See: Alaska State Museum, box 39, folder 689, and Montana Historical Society, box 46, folders 1158-1164
  - Kennedy, Richard, 1964-69 (Box 45, Folder 1074)
  - Kimbrough, Sara Dodge, 1965-66 (Box 45, Folder 1075)
  - Kinney, Doris; Kinney, Jack, 1963-64 (Box 45, Folder 1076)
  - Kirk, Ruth, 1966-67 (Box 45, Folder 1077)
  - Kleiber, Hans, 1959-64, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1078)
  - Knight, Ernest, 1964-65 (Box 45, Folder 1079)
  - Kock, Velma, 1968-72 (Box 45, Folder 1080)
  - Kuchel, Thomas H., 1965 (Box 45, Folder 1081)
  - Kyle, John, 1966-67 (Box 45, Folder 1082)
  - "L" general, 1957-81 (Box 45, Folder 1083-1087)
  - Lakes, Barbara, 1973-74 (Box 45, Folder 1088)
  - Lamb, Margaret Eells, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1089)
  - Lawler, Mary E., 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1090)
  - Leff, Jay C., 1962 (Box 45, Folder 1091)
  - Lehman, Walter, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1092)
  - Leonard, James M., 1959-61 (Box 45, Folder 1093)
  - Lewis and Clark College, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1094)
  - Library of Congress, 1959-65 (Box 45, Folder 1095)
  - Linderman, Wilda, 1964, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1096)
  - Linforth, Frank A., 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1097)
  - Lochrie, Elizabeth, 1960-71, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1098)
  - Lonergan, Tad, 1967-68 (Box 45, Folder 1099)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1962-80 (Box 45, Folder 1100)
  - Los Angeles Public Library, 1964-65 (Box 45, Folder 1101)
  - Lovett, Helen; Lovett, Nancy, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 1102)
  - "M" general, 1959-77, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1103-1112)
  - M. H. de Young Memorial Museum, 1968-72 (Box 46, Folder 1113)
  - M. Knoedler & Co., 1962 (Box 46, Folder 1114)
  - Macaulay, Sarah F., 1965-73 (Box 46, Folder 1115)
  - MacGilvra, E. E., 1962-64 (Box 46, Folder 1116)
  - MacPhail, Norman C., 1963 (Box 46, Folder 1117)
  - Manatt, Sam L., 1976-77 (Box 46, Folder 1118)
  - Marks, Alice, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1119)
  - Marse, John J., 1961-71 (Box 46, Folder 1120)
  - Martin, Harrison T., 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1121)
  - Martinez, Pete, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 1122)
  - Maryhill Museum of Fine Arts, 1960-63 (Box 46, Folder 1123)
  - Maslow, Dorothy, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1124)
  - Maslow, William, Mrs., 1962-63, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1125)
  - Massachusetts Department of Health, 1963-67 (Box 46, Folder 1126)
  - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1965 Nov (Box 46, Folder 1127)
  - McBride, Delbert
    See: Eastern Washington State Historical Society, box 42, folders 893-896, and State Capitol Museum, Washington, box 50, folder 1376
  - McCabe, Frank; McCabe, Mary, 1961-63 (Box 46, Folder 1128)
  - McCall, Tom, 1972 Sep 28 (Box 46, Folder 1129)
  - McCaughen & Burr, Inc., 1962-65 (Box 46, Folder 1130)
  - McClelland, John M., 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1131)
  - McColgan, Neil, Mr. and Mrs., 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1132)
  - McCracken, Harold, 1957-64 (Box 46, Folder 1133)
  - McCurdy, Richard, 1959-60 (Box 46, Folder 1134)
  - McDermott, John Francis, 1964-65 (Box 46, Folder 1135)
  - McElroy, Robert, Mrs., 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1136)
  - McIlwraith, Charles, 1962-64 (Box 46, Folder 1137)
  - McKay, Stanley, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1138)
  - McLure, Katherine, 1963-67 (Box 46, Folder 1139)
  - McNeill, Thomas S., 1961-77, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1140-1145)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1960-63 (Box 46, Folder 1146)
  - Michigan Department of Public Health, 1963-64 (Box 46, Folder 1147)
  - Michigan State Library, 1958-59 (Box 46, Folder 1148)
  - Miles, Charles, 1962-73 (Box 46, Folder 1149)
  - Milhoan, Merle C., 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1150)
  - Miller, Pendleton, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 1151)
  - Mills, Paul
    See: Oakland Museum, box 47, folders 1213-1214, and Santa Barbara Museum of Art, box 49, folder 1337
  - Milwaukee Public Library, 1964-74 (Box 46, Folder 1152)
  - Minneapolis Public Library, 1963-67 (Box 46, Folder 1153)
  - Minnesota Department of Health, 1965-67 (Box 46, Folder 1154)
  - Missouri Historical Society, 1962-66 (Box 46, Folder 1155)
  - Mitchell, Jessie Lincoln, 1962-63 (Box 46, Folder 1156)
  - Montana Gallery Book Shoppe, 1971-72, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1157)
  - Montana Historical Society, 1957-75, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1158-1164)
  - Montana State Board of Health, 1963-64, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1165)
  - Montclair Art Museum, 1959-67 (Box 46, Folder 1166)
  - Montgomery, James, 1963-64 (Box 46, Folder 1167)
  - Montgomery, Richard G., 1972 May (Box 46, Folder 1168)
  - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1967-68 (Box 46, Folder 1169)
  - Moore, Lucia Wilkins, 1963-64 (Box 46, Folder 1170)
  - Mora, Jo, 1963-64 (Box 46, Folder 1171)
  - Morrison, W. M., 1965-66 (Box 46, Folder 1172)
  - Muehlen, John B., 1963 (Box 46, Folder 1173)
  - Muir, Rodney, 1964-67 (Box 46, Folder 1174)
  - Mullan, Read, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1175)
  - Mulvey, Carles, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1176)
  - Mumey, Nolie, 1963-73 (Box 46, Folder 1177)
  - Museo Naval, 1963-65 (Box 46, Folder 1178)
  - Museum of the American Indian, 1963-66 (Box 46, Folder 1179)
  - Museum of New Mexico, 1961-65 (Box 46, Folder 1180-1181)
  - "N" general, 1958-75, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1182-1185)
  - Nash, Faith; Nash, Rodney, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 1186)
  - National Archives and Records Service, 1959-73, n.d (Box 47, Folder 1187-1188)
  - National Cowboy Hall of Fame and Western Heritage Center, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1189)
  - National Gallery of Art (U.S.), 1962-71 (Box 47, Folder 1190)
  - National Gallery of Canada, 1962-65 (Box 47, Folder 1191)
  - National Maritime Museum, Great Britain, 1964-73 (Box 47, Folder 1192)
  - National Park Service, 1960-67 (Box 47, Folder 1193)
  - Nebraska State Historical Society, 1966-67 (Box 47, Folder 1194)
  - Needham, Agnes, 1964-66 (Box 47, Folder 1195)
  - New Jersey Bank, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1196)
  - New Jersey State Department of Health, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1197)
  - New Mexico Department of Public Health, 1962-74 (Box 47, Folder 1198)
  - New Orleans Public Library, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1199)
  - New York City Department of Health, 1964-65 (Box 47, Folder 1200)
  - New York Historical Society, 1962-76 (Box 47, Folder 1201)
  - New York Public Library, 1962-74 (Box 47, Folder 1202)
  - New York State Department of Health, 1963-74, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1203)
  - New York State Historical Association, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 1204)
  - Newberry Library, 1960-73 (Box 47, Folder 1205)
  - Newhouse Galleries, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 1206)
  - Newman, Julia Sweet, 1961-73 (Box 47, Folder 1207)
  - Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 1208)
  - Norling, Ernest, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 1209)
  - Nunis, Doyce B., 1961-63 (Box 47, Folder 1210)
  - "O" general, 1959-76 (Box 47, Folder 1211-1212)
  - Oakland Museum, 1962-78 (Box 47, Folder 1213-1214)
    See also: Ferbraché, Lewis, box 43, folders 923-925
  - Oakland Public Library, 1962-64 (Box 47, Folder 1215)
  - "Occupant", 1962-73 (Box 47, Folder 1216-1217)
  - Ohio Department of Health, 1959-65 (Box 47, Folder 1218)
  - Ohio Historical Society
    See: Duckett, Kenneth, box 42, folder 887
  - Olana Gallery, 1973-75 (Box 47, Folder 1219)
  - Old Dartmouth Historical Society, 1963-66 (Box 47, Folder 1220)
  - Old Print Shop, The, 1958-74 (Box 47, Folder 1221)
  - Oliver, Ruth Koerner, 1964-75, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1222)
  - Oregon Historical Society, 1958-76 (Box 47, Folder 1223-1224)
  - Oregon State Board of Health, 1962-72, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1225)
  - Oregon State Library, 1962-77 (Box 47, Folder 1226-1227)
    Letter of Mar 23 1965 includes
    artist biographies for an exhibit
  - Oregon State University, Department of Art, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 1228)
  - Oregonian, The, 1959-75 (Box 47, Folder 1229)
  - Orton, William, 1967-68 (Box 47, Folder 1230)
  - Ottinger, Martin L., 1962 Jan (Box 47, Folder 1231)
  - Otto Seligman Gallery, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 1232)
  - "P" general, 1958-77, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1233-1239)
  - Pacific County Historical Society
    See: Dixon, Ruth, box 42, folders 877-880
  - Partridge, Elizabeth, 1964-67 (Box 48, Folder 1240)
  - Partridge, Roy, 1964-70 (Box 48, Folder 1241)
  - Paxson, Selia, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 1242)
  - Peabody Museum of Archaeology and Ethnology, 1965-74 (Box 48, Folder 1243)
  - Pearson, Roy T., 1968 (Box 48, Folder 1244)
  - Pease, Lute, 1958-62 (Box 48, Folder 1245)
    See also: Alford, Edith, box 39, folder 691
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1962-67 (Box 48, Folder 1246)
  - Pennsylvania Department of Health, 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 1247)
  - Period Furniture Hardware Company, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1248)
  - Perret, Gertrude, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 1249)
  - Pettus, Terry, 1962-64 (Box 48, Folder 1250)
  - Pinckney, Pauline, 1965-66 (Box 48, Folder 1251)
  - Plowden, Helen, 1959-67 (Box 48, Folder 1252)
  - Poesch, Jessie, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1253)
  - Pollard, Gladys Redwood, 1963-64 (Box 48, Folder 1254)
  - Pollock, Robert W., 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1255)
  - Pomona College Art Department, 1961-73 (Box 48, Folder 1256)
  - Pony Express, 1959-62 (Box 48, Folder 1257)
  - Porter, C. C., Dr. and Mrs., 1963-64 (Box 48, Folder 1258)
  - Portland Art Museum, 1960-75, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1259-1260)
  - Portland Bureau of Health, 1963-72 (Box 48, Folder 1261)
  - Portland Police Bureau, 1967 Oct 3 (Box 48, Folder 1262)
  - Portland State College, 1963-64 (Box 48, Folder 1263)
  - Powell, J. V., 1973 (Box 48, Folder 1264)
  - Powers, Ruth, 1965-75 (Box 48, Folder 1265)
  - Price, Vincent, 1973 Nov 6 (Box 48, Folder 1266)
  - Pritzker, Lee, 1961 Aug (Box 48, Folder 1267)
  - Proctor, Hester, 1962-73, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1268)
  - Proctor, Phimister, 1962 Jun (Box 48, Folder 1269)
  - Provincial Archives of British Columbia, 1959-74, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1270-1272)
  - Prucha, Paul, 1959-67 (Box 48, Folder 1273)
  - Public Archives of Canada, 1958-76 (Box 48, Folder 1274)
  - Public Library of Cincinnati and Hamilton County, 1964-67 (Box 48, Folder 1275)
  - "Q" general, 1959-73 (Box 48, Folder 1276)
  - Quebec Department of Health, 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 1277)
  - "R" general, 1959-85, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1278-1282)
  - Racicot, Ludlow, 1967-68 (Box 48, Folder 1283)
  - Ralston, J. Kenneth, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 1284)
  - Rasmussen, Kermit, 1961-65 (Box 48, Folder 1285)
  - Reddington, Shirley, 1964-66 (Box 48, Folder 1286)
  - Reid, Christine L., 1964-66 (Box 48, Folder 1287)
  - Reiff, Ernest, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1288)
  - Renner, Frederic G., 1961-71 (Box 48, Folder 1289-1291)
  - Reynolds, J. E., 1963-64 (Box 48, Folder 1292)
  - Rhea, V. H., 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1293)
  - Rhodes, Gladys, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1294)
  - Riesenberg, Sidney, 1959-63 (Box 48, Folder 1295)
  - Roach, Rachel, 1963-66 (Box 48, Folder 1296)
  - Roberts, Milnor, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1297)
  - Robinson, L. B., 1965-68 (Box 48, Folder 1298)
  - Robinson, Lillian, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1299)
  - Rochester Paper Company, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 1300)
  - Rockwell Gallery of Western Art, 1964-77 (Box 48, Folder 1301)
  - Rogers, Edward K., 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 1302)
  - Rogers, Fred B., 1960-62 (Box 48, Folder 1303)
  - Roi, Jane, 1964-66 (Box 48, Folder 1304)
  - Root, Marjorie; Root, Robert, 1959-60 (Box 48, Folder 1305)
  - Rosenthal, Sam, 1961-77 (Box 49, Folder 1306-1310)
  - Rosequist Galleries, 1964-72 (Box 49, Folder 1311)
  - Rossin, Edgar, Mrs., 1963-64 (Box 49, Folder 1312)
  - Rothschild, E. E., 1959 (Box 49, Folder 1313)
  - Royal Canadian Academy of Arts, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1314)
  - Royal Geographical Society, 1965-68 (Box 49, Folder 1315)
  - Royal Ontario Museum, 1964-67 (Box 49, Folder 1316)
  - "S" general, 1957-78, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1317-1328)
  - Sackmann, Lulu, 1964-66 (Box 49, Folder 1329)
  - Saddleback Western Art Gallery, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 1330)
  - St. Louis County Historical Society, 1964-66 (Box 49, Folder 1331)
  - Salem Art Association, 1968-70 (Box 49, Folder 1332)
  - Salmagundi Club, 1963-64 (Box 49, Folder 1333)
  - Salt Lake Art Center, 1965-67 (Box 49, Folder 1334)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1962-75 (Box 49, Folder 1335)
  - San Francisco Public Library, 1963-67 (Box 49, Folder 1336)
  - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1962-74 (Box 49, Folder 1337)
  - Sarrett, Jack, Mrs., 1970 (Box 49, Folder 1338)
  - Sartz, Joanne, 1962-63 (Box 49, Folder 1339)
  - Schaeffer, Claude E., 1959-66, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1340)
  - Scheuerle, Joseph, Mrs., 1963-67 (Box 49, Folder 1341)
  - Schlicke, Carl, 1958-59 (Box 49, Folder 1342)
  - Schmeer Insurance Agency, 1961-67 (Box 49, Folder 1343)
  - Schoenberg, Wilfred P., 1959-75 (Box 49, Folder 1344)
  - Schoenfeldt, Arthur, 1975, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1345)
  - Schoonover, Frank E., 1963-76 (Box 49, Folder 1346)
  - Scott, Charles Hepburn, Mrs., 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1347)
  - Seattle Art Museum, 1964-75 (Box 49, Folder 1348)
  - Seattle Public Library, 1962-65 (Box 49, Folder 1349)
  - Seattle Times, 1962-75 (Box 49, Folder 1350)
  - Sedgewick, Thomas, 1963-65 (Box 49, Folder 1351)
  - Shanahan, Isabelle, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1352)
  - Shasta State Historical Monument, 1959-66 (Box 49, Folder 1353)
  - Shaw, Stuart C., 1964-65 (Box 49, Folder 1354)
  - Sheldon Jackson Junior College, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1355)
  - Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery, 1964-74 (Box 49, Folder 1356)
  - Shenson, A. Jess, 1965-68 (Box 49, Folder 1357)
  - Sherwood, Morgan B., 1962-63 (Box 49, Folder 1358)
  - Shorey Bookstore, 1959-65 (Box 49, Folder 1359)
  - Shuler, Mary C., 1961-62 (Box 49, Folder 1360)
  - Shumate, Albert, 1960-75, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1361)
  - Siebert, Frank T., 1961 (Box 49, Folder 1362)
  - Sinclair, J. Gordon, 1966-67 (Box 49, Folder 1363)
  - Singer, Milton, 1960-72, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1364)
  - Smith, Osgood R., 1963-65 (Box 49, Folder 1365)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1958-64 (Box 49, Folder 1366)
  - Smithsonian Institution. Bureau of American Ethnology, 1963-64 (Box 49, Folder 1367)
  - Snowden, Ian, 1959-64 (Box 49, Folder 1368)
  - Society of California Pioneers, 1962-71, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1369-1370)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet, 1974-78 (Box 50, Folder 1371)
  - Specialty Book Concern, 1960-61 (Box 50, Folder 1372)
  - Spokane Public Library, 1963-76, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1373-1374)
  - Stanton, Carey, 1964-65 (Box 50, Folder 1375)
  - State Capitol Museum, Washington, 1966-76, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1376)
  - State Historical Society of Colorado, 1962-73 (Box 50, Folder 1377)
  - State Historical Society of Missouri, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 1378)
  - State Historical Society of Wisconsin, 1962-64 (Box 50, Folder 1379)
  - Stinsman, Edna, 1963-65 (Box 50, Folder 1380)
  - Stone, John, Dr. and Mrs., 1961-63 (Box 50, Folder 1381)
  - Storie, David, 1969, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1382)
  - Stossel, Lee, 1973-76 (Box 50, Folder 1383)
  - Stout, George M., 1962-68 (Box 50, Folder 1384)
  - Stromquist, David, Mrs., 1962-63 (Box 50, Folder 1385)
  - Sullivan, J. M., 1961-63 (Box 50, Folder 1386)
  - Sully, George Langdon, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 1387)
  - Sutton, Leonard V. B., 1967 (Box 50, Folder 1388)
  - Swanson, M. C., 1965-67 (Box 50, Folder 1389)
  - "T" general, 1960-76, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1390-1393)
  - T. N. Luther Books, 1962-66 (Box 50, Folder 1394)
  - Tacoma News Tribune, 1965-75 (Box 50, Folder 1395)
  - Tacoma Public Library, 1960-65 (Box 50, Folder 1396)
  - Taggares, Alice, 1974-77 (Box 50, Folder 1397)
  - Taggart, John, 1970-72 (Box 50, Folder 1398)
  - Tavener, Colin, 1974-76 (Box 50, Folder 1399)
  - Taylor, Ilona, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 1400)
  - Temple, John L., 1959 (Box 50, Folder 1401)
  - Terry DeLapp Gallery, 1960-64 (Box 50, Folder 1402)
  - Thatcher, Hamilton, Mrs., 1964-65 (Box 50, Folder 1403)
  - Thomas, Winifred K., 1963 (Box 50, Folder 1404)
  - Thomas Gilcrease Institute, 1959-73 (Box 50, Folder 1405-1406)
  - Thornton, Mildred Valley, 1966-67 (Box 50, Folder 1407)
  - Tilton Indian Relics, 1959-62 (Box 50, Folder 1408)
  - Time Life Publishing, 1960-75 (Box 50, Folder 1409)
  - Todd, Arlo R., Mrs., 1963 (Box 50, Folder 1410)
  - Topping, Lucille, 1963-64 (Box 50, Folder 1411)
  - Toronto Public Library, 1964-65 (Box 50, Folder 1412)
  - Trailside Galleries, 1958-65 (Box 50, Folder 1413)
  - Tripp, Spencer, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1414)
  - Tucker, Sheldon M., 1967 (Box 50, Folder 1415)
  - "U" general, 1960-79, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1416-1417)
  - Uhthoff, Ina, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1418)
  - Union Pacific Historical Museum, 1963-65 (Box 50, Folder 1419)
  - United States Coast and Geodetic Survey, 1963-64 (Box 50, Folder 1420)
  - United States Government Printing Office, 1967-71 (Box 50, Folder 1421)
  - United States Military Academy, 1964-65 (Box 50, Folder 1422)
  - United States National Museum, 1961-72 (Box 50, Folder 1423-1424)
    See also: Ewers, John C., box 43, folder 911
  - United States Naval Academy Museum, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 1425)
  - University of Alaska, 1958-62 (Box 50, Folder 1426)
  - University of New Mexico, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 1427)
  - University of Oregon Library, 1962-73, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1428-1432)
  - University of Oregon Museum of Art, 1961-66, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1433)
  - University of Oregon Publications, 1960-66 (Box 51, Folder 1434)
  - University of Puget Sound, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1435)
  - University of Southern California, 1963-76 (Box 51, Folder 1436)
  - University of Washington Library, 1959-75 (Box 51, Folder 1437)
  - University of Washington Museum, 1960-76 (Box 51, Folder 1438)
  - University of Washington Press, 1966-72 (Box 51, Folder 1439)
  - University of Wyoming Art Museum, 1971-75, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1440)
  - University of Wyoming Library, 1962-65 (Box 51, Folder 1441)
  - Utah State Historical Society, 1961-67 (Box 51, Folder 1442)
  - "V" general, 1959-75 (Box 51, Folder 1443-1444)
  - Valencia, Irving, 1963-65 (Box 51, Folder 1445)
  - Van Winkle, Edward, Mrs., 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1446)
  - Vancouver Sun, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 1447)
  - Vancouver Art Gallery, 1962-72 (Box 51, Folder 1448)
  - Victoria and Albert Museum, 1961-67 (Box 51, Folder 1449)
  - Virginia State Library, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 1450)
  - Vose Galleries of Boston, 1960-72 (Box 51, Folder 1451)
  - "W" general, 1958-79, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1452-1460)
  - W. D. Harper, Inc., 1965 Oct (Box 51, Folder 1461)
  - Waddell, William R., 1963-64 (Box 51, Folder 1462)
  - Walla Walla Public Library, 1962-63 (Box 51, Folder 1463)
  - Walton, Elisabeth B., 1964-68 (Box 51, Folder 1464)
  - Ward, Edmund F., 1963-73 (Box 51, Folder 1465)
  - Ward, Yvette, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1466)
  - Washington State Department of Health, 1963-75, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1467)
  - Washington State Historical Society, 1959-77 (Box 51, Folder 1468-1469)
  - Washington State Library, 1962-63 (Box 51, Folder 1470)
  - Wearin, Otha D., 1963-65 (Box 51, Folder 1471)
  - Weatherford, H. R., 1965-68 (Box 51, Folder 1472)
  - West, Alta F., 1962-63 (Box 51, Folder 1473)
  - West, Arthur E.; West, Erwin E, Mrs., 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1474)
  - West, Ian, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1475)
  - Western Association of Art Museums, 1959-65 (Box 51, Folder 1476)
  - Western History Association, 1971-73 (Box 51, Folder 1477)
  - Westerners, 1964-69 (Box 51, Folder 1478)
  - Weston, L. M., Mrs., 1966-68, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1479)
  - Weyerhaeuser, J. P., III, Mr. and Mrs., 1963-67, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1480)
  - White Plains Public Library, 1963-73 (Box 51, Folder 1481)
  - Whitman College, 1960-61 (Box 51, Folder 1482)
  - Whitney Gallery of Western Art
    See: McCracken, Harold, box 46, folder 1133
  - Wieghorst, Olaf, 1964-66 (Box 51, Folder 1483)
  - Wildenstein & Co., 1969-70 (Box 51, Folder 1484)
  - Wilder, Mitchell
    See: Amon Carter Museum, box 39, folders 704-712
  - Wilkinson, Rosemary, 1977-79 (Box 51, Folder 1485)
  - Willenborg, Carl, Jr., 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1486)
  - William Rockhill Nelson Gallery of Art (Box 51, Folder 1487)
  - Willis, Louise, 1963-64 (Box 51, Folder 1488)
  - Wills, Irving, 1962-66 (Box 51, Folder 1489)
  - Wilson, Lucille, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 1490)
  - Wire, Melville T., 1963, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1491)
  - Woodward, Arthur, 1961-65 (Box 51, Folder 1492)
  - Woolpert, Walter R.; Woolpert, Lucille, 1964-67 (Box 51, Folder 1493)
  - Worcester Art Museum
    See: De Beaumont, Edmond, box 42, folder 865
  - Wurlitzer, Farny R., 1963-64 (Box 51, Folder 1494)
  - Wyoming State Archives and Historical Department, 1959-67 (Box 51, Folder 1495)
  - Wyoming State Library, 1960-62 (Box 51, Folder 1496)
  - "Y"-"Z" general, 1962-76 (Box 51, Folder 1497)
  - Yates, Myrtle Lee, 1967-69 (Box 52, Folder 1498)
  - Yosemite National Park, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1499)
  - Yost, Karl, 1965-70 (Box 52, Folder 1500)
  - Zeitlin and Ver Brugge, 1964-75 (Box 52, Folder 1501)
  - Unidentified, 1962-76, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1502-1503)
  - Christmas cards, 1962-[80], n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1504-1506)
  - Third party correspondence: Dorsey, Sarah Alden to Mrs. Van Nostrand, 1941 Dec 9 (Box 52, Folder 1507)
- Personal Papers, [1910]-1982; Series VIII; 1.68; (4 boxes)
  Series VIII, Personal Papers, is organized into two
  subseries: Art Collection Papers and Personal Papers.
  The Art Collection Papers are organized into Documents,
  Indexes, Photographs and Other Papers. The Personal
  Papers are organized into Printed Material, Photographs,
  and Other Papers.
  - ART COLLECTION PAPERS
    - Documents
      - Appraisal of Stenzel's art collection, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 1508)
      - Amon Carter loan documentation, 1963-72, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1509)
      - Edmonton Art Gallery loan documentation, 1967 Jun 25 (Box 53, Folder 1510)
      - Insurance form for art sent to Marion County Historial Society, Salem, Oregon, 1965 Apr 4 (Box 53, Folder 1511)
      - "Gift to Montana [Historical Society]. Paxson Appraisal" [and loan documentation], 1963-67, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1512-1514)
      - Portland Art Association loan documentation, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 1515)
      - Portland Art Museum Swan loan - art appraisal, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 1516)
      - Salt Lake Art Center loan documentation, 1965 Oct (Box 53, Folder 1517)
      - Smithsonian Institution Library of the National Portrait Gallery and the National Collection of Fine Arts gift acknowledgment, 1965 Jul 23 (Box 53, Folder 1518)
      - Washington State Historical Society loan - art appraisal, 1965 Apr 15 (Box 53, Folder 1519)
      - "Stolen Art" [newspaper clipping and appraisal], 1960-66, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1520)
    - Indexes
      - Index cards listing information on individual pieces of art in the Stenzel art collection, 1957-64, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1521-1525)
        Accompanied by correspondence,
        receipts, and printed material about
        the artwork
      - Index cards listing information on individual pieces of art in the Stenzel art collection, 1957-64, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1526-1529)
      - Index to the Stenzel art collection (Box 54, Folder 1530)
    - Photographs
      - Copy photographs of the Stenzel art collection, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1531-1535)
        There are also seven folders of
        negatives which are restricted. Some
        of them are represented by copy
        photographs, but many are not. For
        further information, contact the
        Western Americana curator.
      - Copy photographs of art donated to the Russell Trigg Museum, 1968, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1536)
      - Copy photographs of artwork, possibly owned by Stenzel, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1537)
      - Slides for an Alden lecture [?], 1973, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1538)
      - Glass slides of Swan artwork, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1539)
      - Glass slides of western art, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1540)
      - Slides of western art, 1963, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1541)
        Originally found in slide carousel